Da la lun dun
BABY I’mma MONSTER
Mano a mano
I see you in slow mo’
You know you’re in trouble
Ooh hoo hoo hoo
발버둥 쳐봐
Try to get out
어차피 손바닥
I can read you like a book anyway
위에서 못 나가
You know that
When I open my eyes I bloom
눈을 뜬 순간 피어나
All eyes on me
All eyes on me 불을 질러라
Set it on fire
Do or die
On my life
Yeah you ain’t seen nothing yet
Got them all going
Sheesh Sheesh
Sheesh Sheesh Sheesh yeah
B.A.B.Y.M.O.N
Sheesh Sheesh
Sheesh Sheesh Sheesh yeah
Got them all going
Yo hold on 쉿
Yo hold on Shh
걍 들이부어라 네 달팽이관에
Just gonna pour it into your cochlea
이건 네 귀에 줄 축복
This is a blessing to your ears
음악에 맞춰 걍 춤 춰
Just dance to the music
히비리 합 합 boom boom pow
Hibiri hop hop boom boom pow
분위기 타올라 너네들 눈 돌아
Getting hot in here and you guys are gonna flip out
And go crazy
띵하니 적잖이 충격일 거야
Crown this queen
I hit a home run and my next is to the top
홈런은 쳤고 내 다음은 위
Not 5 or 7, I’m 10 out of 10
어중이떠중이 중간 아님
Every mouth is shut when you see me, and say
날 보고 닫혔던 입들 say
Sheesh Sheesh Sheesh
You know what it is
I be running this
Pull up in a ghost
Peek a peek a boo hoo
Vroom vroom
Your heart beat is like pump pump pop
너네 심장에 박동이 pump pump pop
Pedal to the metal
Click clack click
Put’em up to the sky
High high high high
When I open my eyes I bloom
눈을 뜬 순간 피어나
All eyes on me 불을 질러라
All eyes on me
Set it on fire
Do or die
On my life
Yeah you ain’t seen nothing yet
Got them all going
Sheesh Sheesh
Sheesh Sheesh Sheesh yeah
B.A.B.Y.M.O.N
Sheesh Sheesh
Sheesh Sheesh Sheesh yeah
Got them all going
Laugh all you want
마음껏 웃어봐
It’s my turn now
이젠 내 차례니까
Slowly burn it down while you’re asleep
천천히 불태워 네가 잠든 사이
Time’s up Going up higher
Time’s up 올라가 올라가 더
꼭대기 꼭대기로
To the top
하늘 위 하늘 위로
Over the sky
Fly away
온 세상을 뒤집어
Shake up the whole world
Come on let’s ride
BABY I’mma MONSTER
B A B Y M O N
Tell a friend tell a friend tell a friend
Let's go
Jump jump and let it go
Watch out we on a roll
Rum pump pump pump it up then
Jump jump and let it go
Watch out we on a roll
Rum pump pump pump it up then